{
    "subject": "Phyllis_Logan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kevin_McNally",
    "human_readable": "Phyllis Logan is married to Kevin McNally.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9357930421829224,
            "question": "To whom is Phyllis Logan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9335553050041199,
            "question": "Who is Phyllis Logan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9135390520095825,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Phyllis Logan and Kevin McNally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8851206302642822,
            "question": "Who is the spouse of Phyllis Logan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8830226063728333,
            "question": "Name a famous person married to Kevin McNally."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8813596367835999,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Phyllis Logan and Kevin McNally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779842257499695,
            "question": "Who are Kevin McNally and Phyllis Logan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8680893778800964,
            "question": "Is Kevin McNally married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547720670700073,
            "question": "What is the name of Phyllis Logan's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7118231058120728,
            "question": "What is the name of Kevin McNally's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phyllis Logan is married to Kevin McNally.",
            "html": "yago_10658_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Phyllis Logan's husband?",
            "html": "yago_10658_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kevin McNally married?",
            "html": "yago_10658_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Kevin McNally and Phyllis Logan?",
            "html": "yago_10658_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10658_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Phyllis Logan is married to Kevin McNally\":\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents consistently mention that Kevin McNally and Phyllis Logan are married, providing details about their relationship and joint appearances. Therefore, the information in the documents supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Kevin McNally and Phyllis Logan are married. Therefore, the triple \"Phyllis Logan is married to Kevin McNally\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}